realestatetg.com 2011-12-30

# Real Estate Trust Group - Privacy

**_Real Estate Trust Group Privacy_**

**By registering on or visiting the Site, you are acknowledging and accepting this Privacy Policy.** We may from time-to-time revise this Privacy Policy, and the date of last revision will be available at the top of this page, so please be sure to check back periodically. **Your continued use of the Site after changes have been posted to the Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such changes.**

**How We Use Information**

Depending on your use of the Site and the services you request from Real Estate Trust Group, we may use your personally identifiable information for the following purposes: 

·         To enable our Real Estate Trust Group Sales Agents to contact you and provide personal service, or to provide you with personalized content, including email messages, 

·         To facilitate all aspects of the sale and/or purchase (or potential sale and/or purchase) of real estate. 

·         For the purposes for which you provided the information, including to process and respond to inquiries and to contact you about services you have requested. 

·         To improve the content and navigability of the Site. 

·         To solicit your feedback about our services. 

·         To alert you to new Site features, promotions, services, and to deliver other information from which you may opt out. 

·         To enforce the _terms of Use_. 

**The Information We Collect**

Personally identifiable information is information that others can use to identify you, such as your name, address, email address. When you register on and throughout your use of the Site you provide Real Estate Trust Group with certain personally identifiable information including without limitation your name, address, ZIP Code, email address, information about whether you plan on buying and/or selling property, home search criteria, Additionally, Real Estate Trust Group servers automatically record information sent by your browser when you use the Real Estate Trust Group Site, including Internet Protocol address, browser type and language, and date and time of request. We may also collect information using cookies, web beacons or similar technologies.

When you send email or other communication to Real Estate Trust Group, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our service. 

**Third Party Advertising**

Third-party advertisers may serve you ads when you visit the Site. Some of these companies may use information about your visits to Real Estate Trust Group and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

**How We Use Cookies**

A "cookie" is a small data file that can be placed on your hard drive when you visit certain websites. When you visit the Site, Real Estate Trust Group sends one or more cookies to your computer that uniquely identifies your Internet browser. We use cookies to collect, store and sometimes track information for statistical purposes to improve the services we provide. If you are a registered user, we will use a cookie to save your settings and to provide customizable and personalized services. Advertisers and partners may also use their own cookies over which Real Estate Trust Group has no control. 

**How We Protect Information**

Real Estate Trust Group attempts to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of your personally identifiable information. Our servers are protected by reasonable physical and electronic security measures. 

**Links**

The Site may contain links to third-party websites. Real Estate Trust Group is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

**Account Deactivation**

Your Real Estate Trust Group account can be de-activated at any time by contacting  _[ team@RealEstateTG.com](mailto:team@RealEstateTG.com)_,  However, you will not be able to access any of the services offered by Real Estate Trust Group if you choose to deactivate your account. 

**Viewing and Updating Your Information**

You may edit your preferences or request changes to the information you have provided at any time by sending email to [ team@Real EstateTG.com](mailto:team@ziprealty.com) or mail to Real Estate Trust Group, Inc., 2000 Powell Street, Suite 300, Emeryville, CA 94608 or by using the Site. If you have lost your password, you may request a new one by sending an email to  _[ team@RealEstateTG.com](mailto:team@RealEstateTG.com)_. You may also contact your sales agent to edit the information you provide to Real Estate Trust Group. 

**Contact**

If you have any questions, concerns, or suggestions regarding this privacy policy, please contact _[ support@RealEstatetg.com](mailto:privacy@RealEstatetg.com)_.
